spaceglasses.com 2017-12-12

# Privacy Policy

### Effective Date: February 29, 2016

Meta Company, a Delaware corporation (“Meta”), provides this Policy statement explaining its online information practices and the way in which your personal information is collected and used (this “Policy”). By using the Meta Websites or any of the Services, you consent to the practices described in this Policy. Except as explicitly provided herein, this Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Meta does not own or control, or to people that Meta does not employ or manage. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE PRACTICES EXPLAINED IN THIS POLICY, DO NOT ACCESS OR BROWSE THE META WEBSITES, OR USE THE SERVICES. Capitalized terms not defined in this Policy will have the meaning set forth in the Meta Terms of Use, available at <https://www.metavision.com/legal#terms>.

### Collection of Personal Information

The types of personal information collected on the Meta Websites may include, but is not limited to, the following: (1) e-mail address, (2) first and last name, (3) country or region, (4) state or territory, (5) ZIP code or postal code, (6) language, (7) time zone, (8) gender, (9) birth date and age, and (10) occupation. In connection with the purchase of Products and Services, Meta may collect the following additional information (1) billing address; (2) telephone number; (3) where and to whom the Product is shipped; and (4) credit card or other payment information. Meta may also collect and store the IP address of your computer or other networking device, which may be needed to operate various features of the Services or to determine any misuse of content. Meta may also collect data pertaining to your online transactions, purchase history, application usage patterns and website usage patterns by use of a tracking pixel, agent or any other visitor identification technology that collects anonymous data about end users of Meta applications or websites.

### Operational Information

Some “operational” information is used by the Services in order to operate your account properly and provide the Services. This operational information does not include the personal information that you provide as part of your user profile, but may include, for example, the following: the date on which your profile was last updated, whether your e-mail address has been verified, whether your account has been deactivated, what browser you are using, the IP address of your computer or other networking device, and other similar types of information. Operational information may be shared with third parties to the extent necessary to provide the Services.

### Use of Your Personal Information

Meta will not share with, or sell or rent to, others your personally identifiable information, such as your name and e-mail address, without your consent, except as provided herein. Meta may use your personally identifiable information: (a) to deliver you the Services and send you notices related to the Services, your account and necessary updates, (b) to e-mail you promotions and special offers from Meta and its partners, (c) to manage your account and account access, provide you purchase confirmations, support, and customer service and to keep track of support and customer service requests, and (d) to aggregate your information with that of others for marketing and promotional purposes. If you do not want to receive such mailings, you may “opt-out” by the means provided for (if any) in the mailings and/or by changing your personal preferences in your account settings.

In addition, certain promotions and features of the Meta Websites, Software and email correspondence will give the user the ability to opt-in to promotions and special offers to recommend to you for your consideration various products, services, merchandise and upcoming events. Meta may also send you e-mails about periodic service or recommended security updates or surveys related to the Services. These periodic e-mails are considered essential to the provision of the Services you have requested. You cannot unsubscribe from these mailings. You may, however, choose not to participate in the surveys.

### Disclosure of Personal Information

Meta occasionally hires other companies to provide limited services on Meta’s behalf, such as answering customer support inquiries, resolving service problems and correcting errors in the Service (including customer inquiries, billing, and credit corrections), to communicate with you about the Service, to provide you advertising and promotional information in connection with the Service, and to enhance your experience on the Service. Meta will only provide these companies with those pieces of your personal information needed to deliver the Service, and the companies and their employees are prohibited from using that personal information for any other purpose.

Meta may share your personal information with third parties in order to fulfill a service or transaction you may have requested.

Meta may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process served on Meta, including, without limitation, to respond to a subpoena, court order or such other request, or otherwise establish or exercise Meta’s rights; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Meta and of the Content as licensed to Meta; (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Service, or the public; or (d) if Meta files for bankruptcy, or there is a transfer of the assets or ownership of Meta. Meta assumes no obligation to inform you that your information has been provided and in some cases may be prohibited by law from giving such notice.

### Managing Your Personal Information

You can always add, update, or make other changes to the information in your account settings and/or user profile.

### Sharing Your Personal Information

Any information that you may reveal in your user profile, in communication with any other users or in other online discussions or forums, is intentionally open to the public and is not in any way private. You should think carefully before publicly disclosing any personally identifiable information. What you have written may be seen and/or collected by third parties and may be used by others in ways Meta is unable to control or predict.

### Security and Storage of Your Personal Information

Meta uses reasonable precautions to keep user information secure. Meta uses a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. However, due to the open nature of communication through the Internet, Meta cannot guarantee that communications between you and Service, and the Service and you, will be free from unauthorized access by third parties. Users of the Service do so at their own risk. Meta cannot guarantee the security of any information disclosed online.

### Aggregate Information

Meta may collect and analyze information about your use of the Services as aggregated with the use of the Services by other users (“Aggregate Information”); for example, overall usage patterns of Users, the total number of Users, the percentage of Users who are female, or in a certain age range, or who live in a particular region, etc., or the percentage of Users who are also consumers of various other products and services. The collection and analysis of Aggregate Information is important in the operation and enhancement of the Services and other business purposes. Aggregate Information may be compiled in reports and disclosed, sold, licensed or rented to third parties. However, since Aggregate Information does not include any information that can be used to individually identify you or any other User, it is not possible for the third party recipient of the Aggregate Information to use it to identify or contact you.

### Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technology

Meta may collect some information automatically and store it in log files, either directly or through third party analytics providers, such as Google Analytics. This collection may include, but is not limited to: your IP address, browser type and language, device type, referring/exit pages and URLs, other browser history, platform type, number of clicks, landing pages, cookie information, the pages you requested and viewed, the amount of time spent on particular pages, and the date and time of each request you make. A cookie is a very small text file that a website saves to your computer’s hard disk to store information that you provide about yourself or to store your preferences. Meta may place Internet cookies on your hard drive, which may remain on your hard drive until you delete them. Cookies are used to store your profile information on your hard disk. The cookie allows you to move from page to page at the Meta Websites without having to sign in again on each page. You may have the ability to accept or decline cookies using the settings on your browser. However, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use the Services. As part of the Services, Meta may recommend for your consideration various content, products and services. Accordingly, Meta may analyze data pertaining to your online transactions, purchase history, application usage patterns and usage patterns on the Meta Websites through utilizing a tracking pixel, beacon, agent or any other visitor identification technology that collects anonymous data about end users of the Meta Websites and the Services so that Meta can make recommendations suited especially to you or to target certain advertising or promotional offers to you.

Google Analytics uses cookies and pixels in order to collect demographic and interest-level information and usage information from users that visit the Meta Websites, including but not limited to information about the pages where users enter and exit the Meta Websites and what pages users view on the Meta Websites, time spent, browser, operating system, and IP address. Cookies and pixels allow Google to recognize a user when a user visits the Site and when the user visits other websites. Google uses the information it collects from the Meta Websites and other websites and may share that information with us and other website operators – including, but not limited to, age range, gender, geographic regions, general interests, and details about devices used to visit websites and purchase items. Meta does not link information Meta receives from Google with any of your personally identifiable information, or user data. For more information regarding Google’s use of cookies, pixels, and collection and use of information, please review Google’s Privacy Policy. If you would like to opt out of Google Analytics tracking, please visit the following link: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

### Third-Party Websites

The Meta Websites and Services regularly interact with third-party websites, services and applications. Third-party websites, services and applications accessible through the Meta Websites have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of us. Meta has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions. If you provide any information to such third parties, different rules regarding the collection and use of your personal information may apply. Meta strongly suggests that you review such third-party’s privacy policies before providing any data to them.

### Payment Information; Third Party Payment Processor

Credit card payments, including recurring charges, are handled through our third party payment processor. Our third party payment processor will collect and may retain your credit card information in order to process your payment, including payment for your purchases of Products or for any Service charges. We do not control the third party collection, use, disclosure, or retention of your information, including any such actions that might be taken by our third party payment processor. Please review our third party payment processor’s privacy policy and terms of use prior to submitting your payment information.

### Children’s Privacy

A. The Services is not Directed Towards Children. Meta Websites are not intended for use by children. Meta Websites are general audience sites and children under the age of 13 are prohibited from using or registering for an Account on the Site. Meta will not knowingly collect any information from children under the age of 13; nor will Meta send any email correspondence to children under the age of 13. If Meta learns that it has collected information from a child under the age of 13, Meta will remove that information immediately and delete it from our servers. Children under the age of 13 should always ask their parents or guardians before providing their information online. If you believe information from a child under the age of 13 has been submitted to the Meta Websites, please notify Meta at: [privacy@metavision.com](mailto:privacy@metavision.com).

B. California Minors. Meta may provide Meta Website users the ability to publicly post information, for example by submitting user testimonials or other User-Generated Content. If you are a California resident under age 18 and you are unable to remove publicly-available information that you have submitted to Meta, you may request removal by contacting Meta at: [privacy@metavision.com](mailto:privacy@metavision.com). When requesting removal, you must be specific about the information you want removed and provide Meta with specific information, such as the URL for each page where the information is located, so that Meta can find it. Meta is not required to remove any information that: (i) federal or state law requires us or a third party to maintain; (ii) was not posted by you; (iii) Meta anonymizes, so that you cannot be identified; (iv) you don’t follow our instructions for removing or requesting removal; or (v) you received compensation or other consideration for providing the information. REMOVAL OF YOUR INFORMATION FROM THE WEBSITE DOES NOT ENSURE COMPLETE OR COMPREHENSIVE REMOVAL OF THAT INFORMATION FROM META’S SYSTEMS OR THE SYSTEMS OF META’S SERVICE PROVIDERS. Meta is not required to delete the information; Meta’s obligations under California law are satisfied so long as Meta anonymizes the information or renders it invisible to other users and the public.

### California Shine the Light Law

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits California residents to request and obtain from Meta once a year, free of charge, a list of the third parties to whom Meta has disclosed personally identifiable information (as defined under that statute) of that California resident for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year and the categories of that kind of personally identifiable information that was disclosed to them. If you are a California resident and you wish to make such a request, you may do so by contacting us at [privacy@metavision.com](mailto:privacy@metavision.com).

### Reasonable Efforts

Meta will use reasonable efforts to comply with this Policy and will take prompt corrective action when Meta learns of any failure to comply with this Policy. Meta sometimes releases beta versions of Meta’s Products and Services, which are further refined before the release of the final version. Because these products and services are still in a test phase, Meta may not always catch an unintended privacy issue, despite Meta’s efforts to do so. As such, Meta welcomes User feedback on any privacy concerns you may have. In light of the above and because of the complex and constantly changing nature of Meta’s technology and ¬business, and the security risks associated with using the Internet, Meta does not guarantee error-free performance under this Policy.

### Limitation of Liability

TO THE EXTENT PERMISSIBLE UNDER LAW, META WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES RELATING TO THIS POLICY, INCLUDING FOR ANY SECURITY BREACH THAT COMPROMISES ANY USER’S PERSONAL INFORMATION AS IT RELATES TO META’S WEBSITES, SERVERS OR SOFTWARE.

What choices do I have?

You can always opt not to disclose information to use, but keep in mind some information may be needed to take advantage of some of the Services or special features of the Services. You may be able to add or update certain information as explained above. When you update information, however, Meta may maintain a copy of the unrevised information in Meta’s records. You may request deletion of your certain of your personal information by sending an e-mail to [privacy@metavision.com](mailto:privacy@metavision.com). Please note that some information may remain in Meta’s private records after deletion of your account.

If you do not otherwise wish to receive email or other communications from us, please contact us at [privacy@metavision.com](mailto:privacy@metavision.com).

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

Meta reserves the right to modify this Policy at any time. When Meta does so, Meta will also revise the Effective Date at the top of this Policy. Meta encourages you to frequently review this Policy for any modifications. Your use of the Services or Meta Websites after the Effective Date of any updates to this Policy will constitute your acceptance of the updated Policy.

### Contact Us

If you have questions regarding this Policy, please send an e-mail message to: [privacy@metavision.com](mailto:privacy@metavision.com).

Last Updated: 2/29/2017
